{
    "subject": "resource/Gervaise",
    "predicate": "ontology/starring",
    "object": "resource/Maria_Schell",
    "human_readable": "Gervaise stars Maria Schell.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8021193742752075,
            "question": "Who starred in the movie Gervaise?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7002010345458984,
            "question": "What is the name of the actress who starred in Gervaise?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6916595697402954,
            "question": "Is Maria Schell known for starring in movies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5334849953651428,
            "question": "Who directed the movie Gervaise?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45177263021469116,
            "question": "Can you tell me another movie that Maria Schell was in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39771929383277893,
            "question": "What is the plot of the movie Gervaise?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3971305191516876,
            "question": "Are there any awards associated with the movie Gervaise?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3871932327747345,
            "question": "Where was the movie Gervaise filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3850780129432678,
            "question": "What genre is the movie Gervaise likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3632676303386688,
            "question": "When was the movie Gervaise released?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Gervaise stars Maria Schell.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3187_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the movie Gervaise likely to be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3187_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was the movie Gervaise filmed?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3187_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any awards associated with the movie Gervaise?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3187_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3187_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3187_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3187_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3187_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3187_148.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3187_154.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3187_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3187_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3187_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3187_79.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all three documents mention Maria Schell as one of the stars in the film \"Gervaise\", specifically playing the role of Gervaise."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe information provided in the documents states that Maria Schell starred in the film \"Gervaise,\" confirming that she was one of the actors in the movie."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}